[
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 1980sðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Never Gonna Give You Up",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 1980s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Billie Jean",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=Zi_XLOBDo_Y"
  },
   {
    "question": "DECADE: 2020s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Blinding Lights",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=fHI8X4OXluQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 1990s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Wonderwall",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=6hzrDeceEKc"
  },
  {
    "question": "CLASSIC ROCK ðŸŽ¸\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=fJ9rUzIMcZQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ALTERNATIVE ðŸ¤˜\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Smells Like Teen Spirit",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=hTWKbfoikeg"
  },
  {
    "question": "CLASSIC ROCK ðŸŽ¸\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Hotel California",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=EqPtz5qN7HM"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Shape of You",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=JGwWNGJdvx8"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Titanium",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=JRfuAukYTKg"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Shape of You",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=JGwWNGJdvx8"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Call Me Maybe",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=fWNaR-rxAic"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Happy",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=ZbZSe6N_BXs"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Blurred Lines",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=yyDUC1LUXSU"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010s ðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Uptown Funk",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=OPf0YbXqDm0"
  },
  {
    "question": "MOTOWN HITS ðŸ“€\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "My Girl",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=6xKWiCMKKJg"
  },
  {
    "question": "MOTOWN HITS ðŸ“€\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Baby Love",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=oFNo3epm3WU"
  },
  {
    "question": "MOTOWN HITS ðŸ“€\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Bernadette",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=HTtUJUq0VdA"
  },
  {
    "question": "MOTOWN HITS ðŸ“€\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "I Want You Back",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=s3Q80mk7bxE"
  },
  {
    "question": "MOTOWN HITS ðŸ“€\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Superstition",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=0CFuCYNx-1g"
  },
  {
    "question": "RAP & HIP HOP ðŸŽ¤\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Lose Yourself",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=_Yhyp-_hX2s"
  },
  {
    "question": "ELECTRONIC âš¡\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Sandstorm",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=y6120QOlsfU"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2000sðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Hey Ya!",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=PWgvGjAhvIw"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Bad Romance",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=qrO4YZeyl0I"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Like a Prayer",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=79fzeNUqQbQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Vogue",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=GuJQSAiODqI"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Baby One More Time",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=C-u5WLJ9Yk4"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Material Girl",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=6p-lDYPR2P8"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Genie in a Bottle",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=kIDWgqDBNXA"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Bleeding Love",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=Q6k8VVdVLbw"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Don't Speak",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=TR3Vdo5etCQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Halo",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=bnVUHWCynig"
  },
  {
    "question": "POP DIVAS ðŸ‘‘\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Toxic",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=LOZuxwVk7TU"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010sðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Rolling in the Deep",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=rYEDA3JcQqw"
  },
  {
    "question": "ALTERNATIVE ðŸ¤˜\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Enter Sandman",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=CD-E-LDc384"
  },
  {
    "question": "DECADE: 2010sðŸ“…\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Shape of You",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=JGwWNGJdvx8"
  },
  {
    "question": "REGGAE ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡²\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "No Woman No Cry",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=IT8XvzIfiAY"
  },
  {
    "question": "REGGAE ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡²\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "One Love",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=vdB-8eLEW8g"
  },
  {
    "question": "REGGAE ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡²\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Buffalo Soldier",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=2x-oSX6YwX8"
  },
  {
    "question": "REGGAE ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡²\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Red Red Wine",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=J7wHROiC2gQ"
  },
  {
    "question": "REGGAE ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡²\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Stir It Up",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=GM0JW4r7R3s"
  },
  {
    "question": "COUNTRY HITS ðŸ¤ \n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Jolene",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=Ixrje2rXLMA"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Stayin' Alive",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=I_izvAbhExY"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "I Will Survive",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=ARt9HV9T0w8"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Boogie Wonderland",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=3b6GGKuZnJ8"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Night Fever",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=-ihs0a-nh9Y"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Get Down Tonight",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=0GQo2dS1N6g"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Funkytown",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=HRQ2IqlNflM"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Lady Marmalade",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=8wC6UQN-nKE"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Car Wash",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=0g0rKoVZrM8"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "More Than a Woman",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=GIGMNRhx6cA"
  },
  {
    "question": "DISCO ðŸ•º\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Ring My Bell",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=8phch9z8Yso"
  },
  {
    "question": "BOY BANDS ðŸ‘¦\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "I Want It That Way",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=4fndeDfaWCg"
  },
  {
    "question": "BOY BANDS ðŸ‘¦\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Everybody",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=JmmNO0I3XfI"
  },
  {
    "question": "BOY BANDS ðŸ‘¦\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Bye Bye Bye",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=Eo-KmOd3i7s"
  },
  {
    "question": "INDIE ðŸª•\n\nGuess the **song title** from this clip:",
    "answer": "Chasing Cars",
    "url": "https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=GemKqzILV4w"
  }
]
